Viewers all over the world,
faith releases healing anointing.
Faith releases blessing and deliverance.
It is time to build yourself for the journey.
Walking with the Lord - you need faith to walk with the Lord.
Whatever barrier between your heart and the Spirit of God -
the barrier could be pain of the past, bitterness, jealousy, envy, hatred or grief.
Whatever satan uses to connect you to himself -
he uses our barrier to connect us to himself.
He uses offence to connect us to himself.
He uses grief, strife, resentment to connect us to himself.
Whatever satan might have used to connect us to himself, begin to disconnect it!
Disconnect yourself right now!
That offence, be cursed, be removed!
I disconnect you, in the name of Jesus!
Be free!
Say after me,
"Take more of me, oh Lord; give me more of You - more of Your purity, Your holiness, Your faithfulness,
Your humility, Your obedience, in Jesus' name!"
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
RV: Mel Flowers 08/04/2019